okay here we go
[Applause]
[Music]
yes Maya
I should help somebody shot kitchen
forget the if I use the Penniston vendor
in the kitchen in the cows are so my
marriage becomes all my friends
five years that means
if you can study and it's about
protection protection it's going to come
from this comes from this many days to
leave there are three thank you we will
[Music]
okay
someone from my money because you'll
assist
by the way
[Laughter]
Lyra knows for sure but
[Music]
I'm sorry for this boring now let's talk
about coolest and now it's gonna go
deeper and deeper its input is a very
important shoot if you get when you
in the meditation problema becomes
legally problematic cause you try to
find the lingotek sandwich when you're
dying in the spirit shoot so when we
talk about there's three dress
performance shoot some bow three jewels
today race for yes okay number one no my
hands
okay so it's - it's one negative in the
protec here so there's a general so if
homework question you cannot say no that
dharma sangha correct
in English weather put up content in
guestlist and they can read take English
future
[Music]
so I wrote it down
okay so if you okay
[Music]
you have to understand Chuck doesn't
start from Lloyd
[Music]
start their protection the Buddha and
they ran to see the skill of some of
them
[Music]
you can
now we have two fathers two humans the
photos shown of the other circulation
Buddha there's home s cuter Buddha to
house then the endless Angeles City will
yes okay so that's called mission to the
I will not in the temple noise
[Music]
and then put our guest Buddhist can see
oh you know some sentiment that's caused
us and the enemy does in any scene
okay maybe and not fun dear contact has
to say no if you're then you can change
your phone
okay
[Music]
no Palestra no you cannot
okay so when we try to find protection
sufen indecent sustained there's three
kinds of protective to striation via the
kind in CST try you will put actual
armatures like a reporter sama thong so
let's we talked about villager
it's basically this I clicked layer hide
[Music]
inside who get the param order
if a moment had to see they filled when
she put her hand in they momento see -
kinky unfasten it's the Iman device
alignment rented it to a ethnic bandaged
arm and under film super yet see let's
see let's take it down that's its its
own atomic cool film it's just this I'm
Tobias a line because of that white
screen under my alignment lies on layer
is constant film Dennis Lee constant
since I am unarmed I can't believe you
guys are so lazy can escape outside
locos several years ago I told you about
the lady from Singapore from pion hobby
joystick is she Stephane the flower or
Singapore
she also has a white screen
oh yeah yeah - isolative online monte
aabasaheb I know a film in Yemen there
their film but in am under in a plasma
on today I saw Steve and then a man miss
Dickinson site and a posh must-own
techno music now let's see animosities
in dynamic I told you yet Silva's
Benefield minute here to comment on that
site dynamics on to the same distance
Amin - say Cinco Cinco I would almost
feel Medici and Asami you can still kiss
him right those moles of winners with
Sarver that you are not using this
device alignment is the smoother you
will unless we should say madam open the
door when city - irreverent they a man's
activist the political dance I quickly
perfect answer would $400 three
perfectly on 120 froggy froggy froggy
see they Begley fresh take on what they
aiming to be stability cool done is to
say exactly correct
on the Android most so hundred percent
correct me adults on done deal
she said because she will plants good
season disarm implants assist for Rex
Evans Konami sick latisha Naaman says
octopus system better sweet antibodies
wrong sister Nettie and rava 5s una
respuesta muy Dulce paracetamol
[Applause]
- why - a listener to make who is a
throwie solar system because my
diagonally father is this one
multi-systemic mig mining is broken
Buddha I'm an episode the alley on some
kind negativity about this folder you
will see shoots the spotter you will see
my advice alignment this mortal I mean
totally oversize approaching to calm
some told in mania Muslim
before alignment like everyone okay get
skinnier twice you be what sister mom it
is swipe you will stop my teaching
Thomas and Delia you can say the stands
when the City casinos leave us to come
stand a laptop recording the video of
people order the video mentioned alia
this is physical that's Islam is the
sama you bail and it doesn't protect you
directly on this on this condition or
human dome bringing the spooler
technicians so what can protect you must
cut these bishops that's muscle from
both clans the solace from dear Comte
this is the stiffness it's the star my
available in the cruise ship but the
stick we should to me man comes from
Ellen Casey lost her understanding
protect away on thesis 15 we should stay
Air France Safari now my you be Cindy
Lee on my stayin alive
sniff the spool holder their computer ha
students Tom are you bailing on up guys
yeah see bottom understand so Minister
stage does dimensional image math and
for me a common - me I'm funny sauron
I babysit see the ultimate ffff arrived
first aired a sip on mere common the
system I you mine in the star my UV
super but I use a memory like the fact
the Supertop agama you be a super holy
arm for that face all those gates get a
microphone a miss off my leg man a
microphone mid name in bitter the super
to pitama you will detect a farm
Delia heights and for that resource
[Applause]
okay so one day the centum guys then
string snaps like oh my god oh my god oh
that's just come for Nia
Munson DOMA smart viscosity moments the
siping against Pawhuska seeds mustard
event at soybean I don't know
the steely-eyed director found them
talking in the lyrics Connie Mukesh Kai
keep your iron on top harder than she
does to buy it
Buddha a man can do five diverse
Stephanie teeth might be feeling sleep
[Music]
too huh scoffs Ahmed it was an
[Laughter]
accomplished verse that's super but my
you mean it's not off Skiba are you
when you see the directly on vanilla Sun
director first famous blue diamond
Bannister's Vidya built a plow a hope
diamonds hope this child by skip - the
super duper you will buy this in the
Samba available I know stuff on the
stairs aircraft when to toss Affairs son
has to one she said student band shoots
what's the connection between the first
bus system switched in a slide movie
lining it sucked so we can see Etsy
momentum what's the connection between
the first versus the 15 ohms which name
a sentence I'll give a damn rating mum
you say in Spanish necesitas / Sevilla a
Cuidad directamente para poder taken
Verteron dambulla now traffic that you
detective Farren Delia wrong height hop
on some bullets awareness the school
devices that the so City movement
inspired Amma you will see what we are
the rectum ancestors Percy be and Ola
walk without that P it sounds pretty
good either fear stand of yesterday my
economy I hide - you really know much my
situation that's your seat you will know
my eyes direct association so some movie
you are projecting on the then filmed in
the moment of delay revised alignment go
yet
Samson bitching temper you can say start
when simply language the society Larry
vice alignment some implants the
students the first to somebody else why
you be lap discuss first was a state you
later my blank
mighty Larry by sea lion Blanco second
silos
then my especially my nearly arrived I
see line third one okay there's the real
one
there's the real community the sparring
in mineshafts you bail on the snitch
tactic if I trust you will thus I get
mine shafts you will give only - the no
male put up duty start with tiny layer
if I see like the male Dharma guerrillas
left the Safari dama - first a steely
revisal I know missus often six reading
in my toughest the the male but this is
a burnisher unknown and the tracker
morado I went to is fine I am i - Tel
Aviv Gilead
yeah Yaffa hi Thomas
and there's a famous theater dystrophin
on fire so Mia this is to bridge and he
prays of Maya's Emporium fire attack
dimension since on Halloween the houses
and powers in the front end everyone
it's my system obsolete message resonate
so fog light associated I Cooley aye
it's very avoid admin for track I became
tiata angle common signing off here are
the supply cool to show say Vita Talalay
Mouse oh dear oh dear always calm I said
I cannot feel it cost so let's go snooze
brass
[Laughter]
okay
[Music]
that's a symphony which takes four
seconds once again that Sangha Shiva
quality and I never taught them what
hep-c no sorry
and they're not
[Laughter]
is kinda
the word means be noted linear bukas
[Music]
okay so Mark III shuffle dismisses de
try I can shovel of I had definites your
this you will take a mineshaft quality I
don't miss it and I find I'm excited to
try on try quality anxiousness reasons
why I shoved in the fry height and this
one over here
smoker two sets right so some himself
not eat rice or some and confused the
system a stiffness in 63 appears on the
under gripe movies dungeons naturally
Africa wrong song try the fry hydrolysis
this felt day I'm forty tried to summon
gave us on the axis in the admin rights
to summon a fast 21 bias hospital okay
disaster my last year so delish the
table is cheering roseola Farah so fresh
Tina Fey sharpened wisest thing exists
here necessarily ahead so fresh teen
beauty taking on Amanda Julia hi
director
[Music]
leave it is the only massive bomb I
won't sail again it kind of kind of
answer is I'm gonna be kindly mctierney
Universal in in take notice cease to eat
baby I'm knocked about that so I guess
we can say that guy knows a lot of
monkeys are there to fight shotgun
Shenfield
this is it's my day I shaft get mine
shaft the Sangha you will society
disaster ub40 shot was sign okay
[Music]
you have siding off the by confusing you
completely forgot that's two more it's
my move I Thomas three kinds of right I
justify right
decent Davi Erica yeah jack
top men men okay you are free of taqwa
your pure three and this brief neck
arrows okay this is Danny I want to
chill our wort Eldon and person Levi in
donessa to bring in then Linda the mines
Indian
[Music]
an episode about Sunday d Hamid CDC
negative zone and fit in my bin d- naman
zone and shouldn't be in this 19's reach
nirvana different variants were fond of
the bonnets were rights especially
hitting is Leah hi Devon
help you to cure done becomes impossible
be totally negative Navona he put a shot
also along its own the saenggagi -
really - she's the mother for this one
okay because we had we try the citizens
I live - salmon try the fry height
number the elites who summon it was
granted pfft
possibly should sell about to ride a
Milan there are to keep this
alley Keaney is doing alaikum those
who went to the DCI Teacher Training
College TD Bank DCI teacher training
through the DCI we teach a special skill
it's viscosity I shaft
alliteration oh this teacher on tour
use this special a letici Ilia of the
disorder AI and the realistic boost the
piston Singapore Singapore I hate the
fourth octopus we can't manage this
nonsense Oh maestro senior the DCI they
also learn to deal Anunnaki notated
master teacher I stood anyway I'm really
enjoy that we have such a difficult
subject while the Chinese people are
tightly associated steam evasion
ridiculous and gently cops okay we're
missing yet see okay the second of the
second fight it is 570 post a question
that is a sign of guys which restrict
you
[Music]
my own in front tag entity i don4t and
at SOCOM do Shakespeare Festival ihara
paseo stakes TM Primavera hotel Commodus
the second song name for the unsuitable
now my latest on a lonely night in
science so guy inside blade side very
cool this is the body cool
the velocities are climbing come
about schist the sex police vow is a
coulis house okay this is the society a
trial the freiheit the street is not
cheering after service meanwhile the fry
height respect like actual I found one
good the sky-high coffee does the smoke
must like arrests from up there this is
client a taken to hospital yes the
capitate million informational I started
to health the socks Easter on my smart
Tomas nesting it doesn't cross the same
Dennis nor 30 steps look arise it's
released an impersonal Auckland's Mukti
Mishka strong it will offer misters my
name motor dot you did danke basis
what's the my name Dennis is this
feeling so climb has to yet shown the
rise demands even feel you own invention
Chihuahua can
Fionan - hasta Samak so two things
Astrid hinder nice fine institution
contest this is cool yet huh study
technician they finished on the sank two
constants or teen actress Melissa snitch
to the house of Baba no more fears and
es right so salmon autumn artist if the
next input is like these canceled
priorities are here okay let me check if
I finished your first don't work and
then I'll give you a break okay let's
make my shake your the house of Gambia
fatty come on Don convene a power money
powder cumin smoked fair dig oh oh okay
one question I didn't you
ina froggy Massimo's
okay the spot you will apply reroute the
IKE shaft the smart buddha you will have
bribery ike shaft in the press Pauline
is phimosis colorful dry off key
position
I'm sorry
[Music]
for example I say but I need to pay
yes I cough let's put a stool the spice
[Music]
they don't care
about you so blame it like fish they
cannot do it
[Music]
keep teaching the pen
yeah
with revised alignments it cuando una
cerveza Pantheon Blanco Porter